

ABOUT ME

I am a 21-year-old passionate about developing web solutions. I consider myself a productive and diligent person when it comes to the challenges that arise. I strive to perfect my projects once completed and never cease to acquire new knowledge.

CONTACT



54 11 4174-0902



Villa Devoto, CABA.



grinmatias@gmail.com



grinmatias.com.ar



github.com/Zeta2003x



Salesforce trailblazer profile



bit.ly/MGrinLkin

REFERENCES

Pedro Seva pedro_seva@hotmail.com 54 11 3198-2988

LANGUAGE

Native Spanish Advanced English (C2) Conversational Italian

GRIN MATÍAS

Software Developer

With expertise primarily in Salesforce, Python, Javascript, Excel, and Power Bl.

SKILLS

- · Power Bi Word PowerPoint
- HTML CSS Node React
- · C Git SQL UML
- Python (Selenium Flask Pandas)
- · Salesforce (Apex LWC Flows)
- Excel (Power Query VBA)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesforce Developer - Endava

September 2023 - Present

Development of a management system in Salesforce, programming in Apex, LWC (Lightning Web Components), and Flows.

Data Analyst - Symmetria

April - August 2023

Data analysis and reporting in Power BI.

Production planning and control.

Development of a management system in Excel and Visual Basic.

Technical support.

Tech Support - Estudio Grin Bonomo y Asociados

October 2019 - March 2023

Web scraping and process automation with Python and Selenium.

Creation of reports in Power BI.

Analysis and data entry of information related to incident reports.

EDUCATION

UTN-FRBA, Buenos Aires - Arg

Information Systems Engineering 2021 - Present

Colegio Cardenal Copello, Buenos Aires - Arg

High School Studies 2016 - 2020

San Francisco College, Buenos Aires - Arg

English Institute 2011 - 2020